A Guide to the Luther Porter Jackson Papers, 1772-1960
Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
- SERIES IV. ORGANIZATIONAL AFFILIATIONS
  - C. The Association for the Study of Negro Life and History, Inc. 1923-1950
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Rappahannock County 1935-1946 (Box-folder 37:1077)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Richmond County 1940-1948 (Box-folder 37:1078)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Roanoke County 1937-1946 (Box-folder 37:1079)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Roanoke County 1944-1949 (Box-folder 37:1080)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Rockbridge County 1938-1949 (Box-folder 37:1081)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Rockingham County 1939-1946 (Box-folder 37:1082)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Smyth County 1942-1946 (Box-folder 37:1083)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Southampton County 1935-1943 (Box-folder 37:1084)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Spotsylvania County 1935-1946 (Box-folder 37:1085)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Surry County 1937-1950 (Box-folder 37:1086)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Sussex County 1939-1949 (Box-folder 37:1087)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Tazewell County 1942-1949 (Box-folder 37:1088)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Warrick-York County 1935-1950 (Box-folder 37:1089)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Warren County 1938-1947 (Box-folder 37:1090)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Washington County 1942-1944 (Box-folder 37:1091)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Westmoreland County 1940-1949 (Box-folder 37:1092)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Winchester County 1937-1945 (Box-folder 37:1093)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Wise County 1941-1949 (Box-folder 37:1094)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Alexandria City 1937-1945 (Box-folder 38:1095)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Bluefield City 1942 (Box-folder 38:1096)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Bristol City 1939-1945 (Box-folder 38:1097)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Charlottesville City 1935-1949 (Box-folder 38:1098)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. (Box-folder 38:)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Danville City 1937-1944 (Box-folder 38:1099)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. (Box-folder 38:)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Fredericksburg City 1939-1945 (Box-folder 38:1100)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Hampton City 1935-1939 (Box-folder 38:1101)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Hampton City 1940-1949 (Box-folder 38:1102)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Harrisonburg City 1935-1948 (Box-folder 38:1103)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Hopewell City 1936-1946 (Box-folder 38:1104)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Lynchburg City 1935-1949 (Box-folder 38:1105)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Newport News City 1938-1950 (Box-folder 38:1106)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Norfolk City 1942-1946 (Box-folder 38:1107)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Norfolk--B. T. Washington Int. 1935-1946 (Box-folder 38:1108)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Norfolk- B.T. Washington High 1939-1949 (Box-folder 38:1109)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Norfolk--Virginia State College 1946-48 (Box-folder 38:1110)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Norfolk--Douglas Pack 1949 (Box-folder 38:1111)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Norfolk--J. C. Price 1938-1943 (Box-folder 38:1112)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Norfolk--J. H. Smythe 1942-1949 (Box-folder 38:1113)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Norfolk--John T. West 1938-1947 (Box-folder 38:1114)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Norfolk--Laura E. Titus 1940-1946 (Box-folder 38:1115)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Norfolk--Marshall Ave. School 1949 (Box-folder 38:1116)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Norfolk--Paul Lawrence Dunbar 1941-1946 (Box-folder 38:1117)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Norfolk--S.C. Armstrong 1935-1946 (Box-folder 38:1118)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. (Box-folder 38:)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Norfolk--Smallwood 1938-1947 (Box-folder 38:1119)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Norfolk--Titustown School 1938-1946 (Box-folder 38:1120)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. South Norfolk City 1946-1950 (Box-folder 38:1121)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Petersburg City 1935-1942 (Box-folder 38:1122)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Portsmouth City 1937-1950 (Box-folder 38:1123)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Richmond-Armstrong 1938-1949 (Box-folder 38:1124)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Richmond--Baker 1935-1949 (Box-folder 39:1125)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Richmond--Booker T. Washington School 1940-1948 (Box-folder 39:1126)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Richmond--Buchana 1940-1948 (Box-folder 39:1127)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Richmond--City General 1945-1950 (Box-folder 39:1128)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Richmond--Dunbar 1935-1946 (Box-folder 39:1129)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Richmond--Elba 1935-1950 (Box-folder 39:1130)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Richmond--George Mason 1938-1950 (Box-folder 39:1131)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Richmond--Maggie L. Walker 1941-1948 (Box-folder 39:1132)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Richmond--Moore 1935-1950 (Box-folder 39:1133)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. (Box-folder 39:)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Richmond--Navy Hill 1935-1949 (Box-folder 39:1134)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Richmond--Randolph 1939-1947 (Box-folder 39:1135)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Richmond--Sidney 1937-1945 (Box-folder 39:1136)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Richmond--Webster-Davis 1935-1942 (Box-folder 39:1137)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Roanoke City 1930-1944 (Box-folder 39:1138)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Staunton City 1938-1945 (Box-folder 39:1139)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. St. Pauls College 1939-1941 (Box-folder 39:1140)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. St. Pauls College 1942-1944 (Box-folder 39:1141)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Suffolk 1942-1946 (Box-folder 39:1142)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Virginia State College 1939-1942 (Box-folder 39:1143)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Virginia Union University 1941-1945 (Box-folder 39:1144)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Virginia Union University 1935-1940 (Box-folder 39:1145)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Virginia Union University 1946-1949 (Box-folder 39:1146)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Williamsburg City 1939-1949 (Box-folder 39:1147)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Negro History Drive Outside Virginia 1947 (Box-folder 39:1148)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Negro History Drive Outside Virginia 1947 (Box-folder 39:1149)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Negro History Drive Outside Virginia 1947 (Box-folder 39:1150)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Negro History Drive Outside Virginia 1947 (Box-folder 39:1151)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Negro History Drive Outside Virginia 1947 (Box-folder 39:1152)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Postcards 1938-1944 (Box-folder 39:1153)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Miscellaneous 1935-1942 (Box-folder 39:1154)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Miscellaneous 1942-1945 (Box-folder 39:1155)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Miscellaneous 1946 (Box-folder 39:1156)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Miscellaneous 1946 (Box-folder 39:1157)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Miscellaneous 1947-1949 (Box-folder 39:1158)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Annual Report 1937-1939 (Box-folder 39:1160)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Annual Report 1941-1942 (Box-folder 39:1161)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Annual Report 1946-1947 (Box-folder 39:1162)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Annual Report 1948-1949 (Box-folder 39:1163)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Report 1935-1937 (Box-folder 39:1164)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. (Box-folder 39:)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Report 1936-1940 (Box-folder 39:1165)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Report 1941 (Box-folder 39:1166)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Report 1942-1943 (Box-folder 39:1167)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Report 1944 (Box-folder 39:1168)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Report 1941-1945 (Box-folder 39:1169)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Report 1944-1946 (Box-folder 39:1170)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Report 1947-1948 (Box-folder 39:1171)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Membership List 1936-1937 (Box-folder 39:1172)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Program 1944 (Box-folder 39:1173)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Press Release 1947 (Box-folder 39:1174)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Annual Report 1937-1939 (Box-folder 40:1160)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Annual Report 1941-1942 (Box-folder 40:1161)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Annual Report 1946-1947 (Box-folder 40:1162)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Annual Report 1948-1949 (Box-folder 40:1163)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Report 1935-1937 (Box-folder 40:1164)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Report 1936-1940 (Box-folder 40:1165)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Report 1941 (Box-folder 40:1166)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Report 1942-1943 (Box-folder 40:1167)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Report 1944 (Box-folder 40:1168)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Report 1941-1945 (Box-folder 40:1169)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Report 1944-1946 (Box-folder 40:1170)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Report 1947-1948 (Box-folder 40:1171)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Membership List 1936-1937 (Box-folder 40:1172)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Program 1944 (Box-folder 40:1173)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Press Release 1947 (Box-folder 40:1174)
    - Financial Statement 1921-1922 (Box 41)
    - Annual Report 1935-1936 (Box 41)
    - Annual Report 1936-1937 (Box 41)
    - Annual Report 1939-1940 (Box 41)
    - Annual Report 1940-1941 (Box 41)
    - Collecting Funds in Virginia 1940 (Box 41)
    - Collecting Funds in Virginia n.d. (Box 41)
    - Collecting Funds in Virginia 1945 (Box 41)
    - Home Study Department n.d. (Box 41)
    - Annual Meeting 1927 (Box 41)
    - Annual Meeting 1929 (Box 41)
    - Annual Meeting 1930 (Box 41)
    - Annual Meeting 1932 (Box 41)
    - Annual Meeting 1937 (Box 41)
    - Annual Meeting 1938 (Box 41)
    - Annual Meeting 1940 (Box 41)
    - Annual Meeting 1941 (Box 41)
    - Annual Meeting 1942 (Box 41)
    - Annual Meeting 1943 (Box 41)
    - Annual Meeting 1944 (Box 41)
    - Annual Meeting 1947 (Box 41)
    - Negro History Week 1935 (Box 41)
    - Negro History Week 1936 (Box 41)
    - Negro History Week 1937 (Box 41)
    - Negro History Week 1949 (Box 41)
    - Business Inspiration: Dr. Carter G. Woodson Stamps 1947 (Box 41)
  - D. The N.A.A.C.P.
    - N.A.A.C.P. Correspondence 1937 (Box-folder 42:1175)
    - N.A.A.C.P. Correspondence 1938 (Box-folder 42:1175a)
    - N.A.A.C.P. Correspondence 1939 (Box-folder 42:1176)
    - N.A.A.C.P. Correspondence 1941 (Box-folder 42:1177)
    - N.A.A.C.P. Correspondence 1942 (Box-folder 42:1178)
    - N.A.A.C.P. Correspondence 1943 (Box-folder 42:1179)
    - N.A.A.C.P. Correspondence 1944 (Box-folder 42:1180)
    - N.A.A.C.P. Correspondence 1945 (Box-folder 42:1181)
    - N.A.A.C.P. Correspondence 1946 (Box-folder 42:1182)
    - N.A.A.C.P. Correspondence 1946 (Box-folder 42:1183)
    - N.A.A.C.P. Correspondence 1947 (Box-folder 42:1184)
    - N.A.A.C.P. Correspondence 1947 (Box-folder 42:1185)
    - N.A.A.C.P. Correspondence 1947 (Box-folder 42:1186)
    - N.A.A.C.P. Correspondence 1948 (Box-folder 42:1187)
    - N.A.A.C.P. Correspondence 1948 (Box-folder 42:1188)
    - N.A.A.C.P. Correspondence 1948 (Box-folder 42:1189)
    - N.A.A.C.P. Correspondence 1949 (Box-folder 42:1190)
    - N.A.A.C.P. Correspondence 1949 (Box-folder 42:1191)
    - N.A.A.C.P. Correspondence 1950 (Box-folder 42:1192)
    - N.A.A.C.P. Correspondence n.d. (Box-folder 42:1193)
    - N.A.A.C.P. Correspondence: Petersburg 1943-1947 (Box-folder 42:1194)
    - N.A.A.C.P. Petersburg List n.d. (Box-folder 42:1195)
    - N.A.A.C.P. Notes/Notes List n.d. (Box-folder 42:1196)
    - N.A.A.C.P. Notes/Notes List n.d. (Box-folder 42:1197)
    - N.A.A.C.P. Notes/Notes List n.d. (Box-folder 42:1198)
    - N.A.A.C.P. Financial n.d. (Box-folder 42:1199)
    - N.A.A.C.P. Minutes 1947 (Box-folder 42:1200)
  - E. I.B.P.O.E.W. of W. (the Elks)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Correspondence 1943 (Box-folder 43:1201)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Correspondence 1944 (Box-folder 43:1202)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Correspondence 1945 (Box-folder 43:1203)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Correspondence 1946 (Box-folder 43:1204)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Correspondence 1947 (Box-folder 43:1205)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Correspondence 1948 (Box-folder 43:1206)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Correspondence 1949 (Box-folder 43:1207)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Correspondence 1950 (Box-folder 43:1208)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Correspondence n.d. (Box-folder 43:1209)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Reports (Box-folder 43:1210)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Membership Roster (Box-folder 43:1211)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. (Box-folder 43:)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Alexander 1943-1948 (Box-folder 43:1212)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Arlington 1944-1945 (Box-folder 43:1213)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Ashland South Anna 1948 (Box-folder 43:1214)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Berryville 1946 (Box-folder 43:1215)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Charlottesville (Rivanna) 1942-1948 (Box-folder 43:1216)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Chase City 1944-1948 (Box-folder 43:1217)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Churchland (Innerlight) 1948 (Box-folder 43:1218)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Covington 1947 (Box-folder 43:1219)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Danville 1943-1949 (Box-folder 43:1220)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Fredericksburg 1947 (Box-folder 43:1221)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Sassafias (Gloucester Lodge) 1948 (Box-folder 43:1222)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Hampton (Exclusion) 1941-1948 (Box-folder 43:1223)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Hopewell 1941 (Box-folder 43:1224)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Lawrenceville 1948 (Box-folder 43:1225)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Lunenburg 1946 (Box-folder 43:1226)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Lynchburg 1944-1947 (Box-folder 43:1227)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Mecklenburg 1944 (Box-folder 43:1228)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Newport News 1946 (Box-folder 43:1229)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Newport News 1947-1948 (Box-folder 43:1230)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Norfolk 1943-1948 (Box-folder 43:1231)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Nottoway 1946 (Box-folder 43:1232)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Henry (Patrick Henry) 1948 (Box-folder 43:1233)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Petersburg 1944-1947 (Box-folder 43:1234)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Pocahontas 1948 (Box-folder 43:1235)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Portsmouth 1945-1948 (Box-folder 43:1236)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Prince Edward 1945-1946 (Box-folder 43:1237)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Farmville (Prince Edward) 1948 (Box-folder 43:1238)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Richmond 1943-1948 (Box-folder 43:1239)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Staunton 1945-1947 (Box-folder 43:1240)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Suffolk 1941-1948 (Box-folder 43:1241)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Surry 1945-1948 (Box-folder 43:1242)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Warrentown 1944-1948 (Box-folder 43:1243)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Winchester 1944-1946 (Box-folder 43:1244)
    - I.B.P.O.E.W. Zuni 1948 (Box-folder 43:1245)
  - F. The Virginia World War II History Commission 1944-1948
    - Virginia History Commission Correspondence 1944 (Box-folder 44:1246)
    - Virginia History Commission Correspondence 1945 (Box-folder 44:1247)
    - Virginia History Commission Correspondence 1945 (Box-folder 44:1248)
    - Virginia History Commission Correspondence 1946 (Box-folder 44:1249)
    - Virginia History Commission Correspondence 1946 (Box-folder 44:1250)
    - Virginia History Commission Correspondence 1946 (Box-folder 44:1251)
    - Virginia History Commission Correspondence 1947 (Box-folder 44:1252)
    - Virginia History Commission Correspondence 1947 (Box-folder 44:1253)
    - Virginia History Commission Correspondence 1947 (Box-folder 44:1254)
    - Virginia History Commission Correspondence A 1945 (Box-folder 44:1255)
    - Virginia History Commission Correspondence B 1946 (Box-folder 44:1256)
    - Virginia History Commission Correspondence C 1946 (Box-folder 44:1257)
    - Virginia History Commission Correspondence D n.d. (Box-folder 44:1258)
    - Virginia History Commission Correspondence E n.d. (Box-folder 44:1259)
    - Virginia History Commission Correspondence F n.d. (Box-folder 44:1260)
    - Virginia History Commission Correspondence G 1944 (Box-folder 44:1261)
    - Virginia History Commission Correspondence H n.d. (Box-folder 44:1262)
    - Virginia History Commission Correspondence J n.d. (Box-folder 44:1263)
    - Virginia History Commission Correspondence K n.d. (Box-folder 44:1264)
    - Virginia History Commission Correspondence L n.d. (Box-folder 44:1265)
    - Virginia History Commission Correspondence M n.d. (Box-folder 44:1266)
    - Virginia History Commission Correspondence N n.d. (Box-folder 44:1267)
    - Virginia History Commission Correspondence P n.d. (Box-folder 44:1268)
    - Virginia History Commission Correspondence R n.d. (Box-folder 44:1269)
    - Virginia History Commission Correspondence S 1946 (Box-folder 44:1270)
    - Virginia History Commission Correspondence W 1946 (Box-folder 44:1271)
  - G. The Southern Regional Council
    - Southern Regional Council Correspondence 1942-1943 (Box-folder 44:1272)
    - Southern Regional Council Correspondence 1943 (Box-folder 44:1273)
    - Southern Regional Council Correspondence 1944 (Box-folder 44:1274)
    - Southern Regional Council Correspondence 1945 (Box-folder 44:1275)
    - Southern Regional Council Correspondence 1945 (Box-folder 44:1276)
    - Southern Regional Council Correspondence 1947 (Box-folder 45:1277)
    - Southern Regional Council Correspondence 1948 (Box-folder 45:1278)
    - Southern Regional Council Correspondence 1949 (Box-folder 45:1279)
    - Southern Regional Council Correspondence 1950 (Box-folder 45:1280)
    - Southern Regional Council Minutes 1943 (Box-folder 45:1281)
    - Southern Regional Council Minutes 1945 (Box-folder 45:1282)
    - Southern Regional Council Minutes 1947 (Box-folder 45:1283)
    - Southern Regional Council Minutes 1949 (Box-folder 45:1284)
    - Southern Regional Council Report n.d. (Box-folder 45:1285)
    - Southern Regional Council Financial n.d. (Box-folder 45:1286)
    - Southern Regional Council Covenant 1943 (Box-folder 45:1287)
    - Southern Regional Council Bulletin n.d. (Box-folder 45:1288)
    - Southern Regional Council Mailing List n.d. (Box-folder 45:1289)
    - Southern Regional Council Durham Conference n.d. (Box-folder 45:1290)
    - Southern Regional Council Meetings n.d. (Box-folder 45:1291)
  - H. The Negro Organizational Society
    - N.O.S. Correspondence 1941 (Box-folder 46:1292)
    - N.O.S. Correspondence 1942 (Box-folder 46:1293)
    - N.O.S. Correspondence 1943 (Box-folder 46:1294)
    - N.O.S. Correspondence 1944 (Box-folder 46:1295)
    - N.O.S. Correspondence 1945 (Box-folder 46:1296)
    - N.O.S. Correspondence 1946 (Box-folder 46:1297)
    - N.O.S. Correspondence 1947 (Box-folder 46:1298)
    - N.O.S. Correspondence 1948 (Box-folder 46:1299)
    - N.O.S. Correspondence 1949 (Box-folder 46:1300)
    - N.O.S. Correspondence 1950 (Box-folder 46:1301)
    - N.O.S. Minutes 1944 (Box-folder 46:1302)
    - N.O.S. Minutes 1945 (Box-folder 46:1303)
    - N.O.S. Minutes 1946 (Box-folder 46:1304)
    - N.O.S. Minutes 1947 (Box-folder 46:1305)
    - N.O.S. Minutes 1948 (Box-folder 46:1306)
    - N.O.S. Minutes 1949 (Box-folder 46:1307)
    - N.O.S. Reports 1944 (Box-folder 46:1308)
    - N.O.S. Reports 1945 (Box-folder 46:1309)
    - N.O.S. Reports 1946 (Box-folder 46:1310)
    - N.O.S. Financial n.d. (Box-folder 46:1311)
    - N.O.S. List n.d. (Box-folder 46:1312)
    - N.O.S. Newsletter n.d. (Box-folder 46:1313)
  - I. The Committee for Virginia
    - Committee for Virginia Correspondence 1944-1945 (Box-folder 46:1314)
    - Committee for Virginia Correspondence 1946 Jan-Mar (Box-folder 46:1315)
    - Committee for Virginia Correspondence 1946 April (Box-folder 46:1316)
    - Committee for Virginia Correspondence 1946 May-Jul (Box-folder 46:1317)
    - Committee for Virginia Correspondence 1946 Aug-Dec (Box-folder 46:1318)
    - Committee for Virginia Correspondence 1947 Jan-Apr (Box-folder 46:1319)
    - Committee for Virginia Correspondence 1947 Apr-Jul (Box-folder 46:1320)
    - Committee for Virginia Correspondence 1947 Aug-Nov (Box-folder 46:1321)
    - Committee for Virginia Correspondence 1947 Dec (Box-folder 46:1322)
    - Committee for Virginia Correspondence 1948 Jan (Box-folder 46:1323)
    - Committee for Virginia Correspondence 1948 Feb-Nov (Box-folder 46:1324)
    - Committee for Virginia Correspondence 1948 Dec (Box-folder 46:1325)
    - Committee for Virginia Correspondence 1949 Jan-Nov (Box-folder 46:1326)
    - Committee for Virginia Correspondence 1950 (Box-folder 46:1327)
    - Committee for Virginia Correspondence n.d. (Box-folder 46:1328)
    - Committee for Virginia Minutes 1946-1947 (Box-folder 46:1329)
    - Committee for Virginia Proposal n.d. (Box-folder 46:1330)
    - Committee for Virginia Reports 1944-1949 (Box-folder 47:1331)
    - Committee for Virginia Financial Reports 1947-1948 (Box-folder 47:1332)
    - Committee for Virginia Financial Reports 1947 (Box-folder 47:1333)
    - Committee for Virginia Financial Reports 1947 (Box-folder 47:1334)
    - Committee for Virginia Printed 1947-1948 (Box-folder 47:1335)
    - Committee for Virginia Conference Programs 1950 (Box-folder 47:1336)
  - J. The Petersburg Negro Business League
    - Petersburg Negro Business League Correspondence 1937-39 (Box-folder 48:1337)
    - Petersburg Negro Business League Correspondence 1940 (Box-folder 48:1338)
    - Petersburg Negro Business League Correspondence 1941 (Box-folder 48:1339)
    - Petersburg Negro Business League Correspondence 1942-43 (Box-folder 48:1340)
    - Petersburg Negro Business League Correspondence 1945 (Box-folder 48:1341)
    - Petersburg Negro Business League Article 1941 (Box-folder 48:1342)
    - Petersburg Negro Business League Report 1938 (Box-folder 48:1343)
  - K. The Virginia Society for Research
    - Virginia Society for Research Constitution n.d. (Box-folder 48:1344)
    - Virginia Society for Research Treasurer's Report 1944 (Box-folder 48:1345)
    - Virginia Society for Research Jackson-Mitchell 1942-1943 (Box-folder 48:1346)
    - Virginia Society for Research Jackson-Mitchell 1943 Nov-Dec (Box-folder 48:1347)
    - Virginia Society for Research Jackson-Mitchell 1944 Sep-Oct (Box-folder 48:1348)
    - Virginia Society for Research Jackson-Mitchell 1944 Nov (Box-folder 48:1349)
    - Virginia Society for Research Jackson-Mitchell 1945 Oct-Nov (Box-folder 48:1350)
    - Virginia Society for Research Jackson-Mitchell 1946 Oct-1950 (Box-folder 48:1351)
  - L. The Petersburg Community Chorus
    - The Petersburg Community Chorus History n.d. (Box-folder 48:1352)
    - The Petersburg Community Chorus Financial Report 1940-1941 (Box-folder 48:1353)
    - The Petersburg Community Chorus Roster n.d. (Box-folder 48:1354)
    - The Petersburg Community Chorus Roster n.d. (Box-folder 48:1355)
    - The Petersburg Community Chorus Roster n.d. (Box-folder 48:1356)
  - M. The Southern School for Workers 1944-1949
    - The Southern School for Workers Correspondence 1944-47 (Box-folder 48:1357)
    - The Southern School for Workers Correspondence 1948 (Box-folder 48:1358)
    - The Southern School for Workers Correspondence 1949 (Box-folder 48:1359)
  - N. The Old Dominion Medical Society
    - Old Dominion Medical Society Roster n.d. (Box-folder 48:1360)
    - Petersburg Interracial Committee Constitution 1948 (Box-folder 48:1361)
  - O. The Petersburg Interracial Committee 1948
    - Commission on Interracial Cooperation, Inc. 1943 (Box-folder 48:1362)
    - Commission on Interracial Cooperation, Inc. 1943 (Box-folder 48:1363)
    - Commission on Interracial Cooperation, Inc. 1943 (Box-folder 48:1364)
    - Commission on Interracial Cooperation, Inc. 1943 (Box-folder 48:1365)
    - Commission on Interracial Cooperation, Inc. 1943 (Box-folder 48:1366)
    - Commission on Interracial Cooperation, Inc. 1944 (Box-folder 48:1367)